(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(16)},16:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(1),s=n(2),r=n(4),i=n(3),o=n(5),c=n(0),u=n.n(c),l=n(8),d=n.n(l),h=(n(7),n(9)),m=n.n(h),p=[{question:"Leeds, United Kingdom is the birthplace of what Borussen?",answers:["Marwin Hitz","Jadon Sancho","Manuel Akanji","Erling Braut H\xe5land"],correct:"Erling Braut H\xe5land",questionId:"099099"},{question:"Paco Alc\xe1cer was born in",answers:["Petra, Spain","Braga, Portugal","Torrent, Spain","Madrid, Spain"],correct:"Torrent, Spain",questionId:"183452"},{question:"With 127 goals, this player is 7th on Dortmund's all-time top 10 goalscorers",answers:["Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang","Marco Reus","J\xfcrgen Sch\xfctz","Lothar Emmerich"],correct:"Marco Reus",questionId:"267908"},{question:"Nuri Sahin became the Bundesliga's youngest scorer at what age?",answers:["16 years & 238 days","17 years & 82 days","16 years & 334 days","17 years & 37 days"],correct:"17 years & 82 days",questionId:"333247"},{question:"What year did the Westfalenstadion open?",answers:["1972","1978","1974","1975"],correct:"1974",questionId:"496293"},{question:"Ewerthon scored the goal to give Borussia Dortmund the lead over Bremen after only being on for _____.",answers:["1 minute 4 seconds","49 seconds","1 minute 23 seconds","38 seconds"],correct:"49 seconds",questionId:"588909"},{question:"Borussia Dortmund finished at the top of the table with ____ in the 11/12 season.",answers:["81 points","75 points","78 points","80 points"],correct:"81 points",questionId:"648452"},{question:"Cruising to a 4-1 victory, beating which team in the final of the 1988-89 DFB-Pokal?",answers:["VfB Stuttgart","FC Bayern","Werder Bremen","Bayer 04"],correct:"Werder Bremen",questionId:"786649"},{question:"After how many years did Borussia Dortmund get their first win against Sch*lke?",answers:["18","3","7","23"],correct:"18",questionId:"839754"},{question:"With 10 goals this player is the top time scorer in the Revierderby?",answers:["Ingo Anderbr\xfcgge","Michael Zorc","Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang","Lothar Emmerich"],correct:"Lothar Emmerich",questionId:"98390"},{question:"Which player is a noted Dragon Ball fan?",answers:["Hakimi","Zaga","Sancho","Dahoud"],correct:"Zaga",questionId:"1071006"},{question:"This player is red-green colorblind?",answers:["Julian Brandt","Roman B\xfcrki","Thomas Delaney","Marco Reus"],correct:"Thomas Delaney",questionId:"1174154"},{question:"Which player was not apart of the 10/11 champion team",answers:["Ilkay G\xfcndogan","Lukasz Piszczek","Mario G\xf6tze","Mitchell Langerak"],correct:"Ilkay G\xfcndogan",questionId:"1226535"},{question:"Which player was not in the 94/95 champion team?",answers:["Andreas M\xf6ller","Stefan Klos","Matthias Sammer","Marco Kurz"],correct:"Marco Kurz",questionId:"1310938"},{question:"Lucien Favre was born in",answers:["Wiesendangen, Switzerland","Saint-Barthelemy, Switzerland","M\xfcnsingen, Switzerland","St. Gallen, Switzerland"],correct:"Skin",questionId:"1436873"},{question:"Lucien Favre became the first ever manager to remain unbeaten for how many Bundesliga matches",answers:["10","20","15","18"],correct:"15",questionId:"1515110"},{question:"What is the capacity of the Westfalenstadion?",answers:["81365","81455","81220","81565"],correct:"81365",questionId:"1642728"},{question:"Borussia Dortmund returned to the Bundesliga in?",answers:["1973","1975","1976","1978"],correct:"1976",questionId:"1747256"},{question:"Which company has not been a supplier of Dortmund kits?",answers:["Adidas","Nike","Kappa","Umbro"],correct:"Umbro",questionId:"1822532"},{question:"B\u0142aszczykowski was plagued by a torn leg muscle in which season?",answers:["2008-09","2009-10","2010-11","2012-13"],correct:"2008-09",questionId:"195075"},{question:"On 1 August 2016 B\u0142aszczykowski joined Wolfsburg for?",answers:["\u20ac4 million ","\u20ac8 million","\u20ac5 million","\u20ac12 million"],correct:"\u20ac5 million",questionId:"2019778"},{question:"Shinji Kagawa initially joined Borussia Dortmund for?",answers:["\u20ac3.5 million","\u20ac350,000","\u20ac700,000","\u20ac5 million"],correct:"\u20ac350,000",questionId:"2134343"},{question:"Christian Pulisic joined Chelsea in 2019 for a fee of?",answers:["\u20ac64 million","\u20ac50 million","\u20ac46 million","\u20ac75 million"],correct:"\u20ac64 million",questionId:"2210799"},{question:"When is Marco Reus' birthday?",answers:["October 31","July 6","February 29","May 31"],correct:"May 31",questionId:"2379831"},{question:"Which manager signed Guerreiro?",answers:["Tuchel","St\xf6ger","Favre","Bosz"],correct:"Tuchel",questionId:"2426418"},{question:"How fast did Erling H\xe5land score a hattrick on his debut?",answers:["45 minutes","23 minutes","36 minutes","12 minutes"],correct:"23 minutes",questionId:"2510086"}],w=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:1;return Promise.resolve(p.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},q=function(e){function t(){return Object(a.a)(this,t),Object(r.a)(this,Object(i.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(o.a)(t,e),Object(s.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return u.a.createElement("div",null,u.a.createElement("h1",{className:"question"},this.props.text))}}]),t}(c.Component),y=function(e){function t(){return Object(a.a)(this,t),Object(r.a)(this,Object(i.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(o.a)(t,e),Object(s.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return u.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-board"},u.a.createElement("h1",{className:"score"},"You scored ",this.props.text,"/5"))}}]),t}(c.Component),f=n(10),g=function(e){var t=e.options,n=e.selected,a=Object(c.useState)(t),s=Object(f.a)(a,2),r=s[0],i=s[1];return u.a.createElement("div",null,r.map((function(e,t){return u.a.createElement("button",{key:t,className:"answerBtn",onClick:function(){n(e),i([e])}},e)})))},b=function(e){function t(){var e,n;Object(a.a)(this,t);for(var s=arguments.length,o=new Array(s),c=0;c<s;c++)o[c]=arguments[c];return(n=Object(r.a)(this,(e=Object(i.a)(t)).call.apply(e,[this].concat(o)))).state={questionBank:[],score:0,responses:0,questionNum:0,q:"",answers:"",id:0,selectedA:""},n.getQuestions=function(){w().then((function(e){n.setState({questionBank:e});var t=n.state.questionBank;n.setState({q:t[0].question}),n.setState({answers:t[0].answers}),n.setState({id:t[0].id})}))},n.checkAnswer=function(e,t,a,s){s===a&&(console.log(s+"  "+a),e++,n.state.score=e),n.setState({score:e}),console.log(n.state.score),t++,n.state.responses=t,console.log("responses: "+n.state.responses),n.checkGame(t)},n}return Object(o.a)(t,e),Object(s.a)(t,[{key:"checkGame",value:function(e){this.getQuestions()}},{key:"startGame",value:function(){this.getQuestions(),this.setState({score:0})}},{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.startGame()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;switch(this.state.responses){case 5:return u.a.createElement("div",null,u.a.createElement(y,{text:this.state.score}),u.a.createElement("button",{className:"playBtn",onClick:function(){return window.location.reload(!1)}},"Return to Menu"));default:return u.a.createElement("div",{className:"mainCon"},u.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},u.a.createElement(q,{className:"question",text:this.state.q}),this.state.questionBank.map((function(t){var n=t.answers,a=t.correct,s=t.questionId;return u.a.createElement(g,{options:n,key:s,selected:function(t){return e.checkAnswer(e.state.score,e.state.responses,t,a)}})}))))}}}]),t}(c.Component),k=function(e){function t(){var e,n;Object(a.a)(this,t);for(var s=arguments.length,o=new Array(s),c=0;c<s;c++)o[c]=arguments[c];return(n=Object(r.a)(this,(e=Object(i.a)(t)).call.apply(e,[this].concat(o)))).state={renderView:!1},n.clickBtn=function(e){!1===n.state.renderView?n.setState({renderView:!0}):n.setState({renderView:!1})},n}return Object(o.a)(t,e),Object(s.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){switch(this.state.renderView){case!0:return u.a.createElement(b,null);default:return u.a.createElement("div",{className:"menuCon"},u.a.createElement("h1",{className:"title"},"Dortmund Trivia Quiz"),u.a.createElement("img",{className:"img",alt:"logo",src:m.a}),u.a.createElement("br",null),u.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn",onClick:this.clickBtn},"Start Quiz"))}}}]),t}(c.Component),v=document.getElementById("root");d.a.render(u.a.createElement(k,null),v)},7:function(e,t,n){},9:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n.p+"static/media/Germany_Team_Vector.bd838279.svg"}},[[11,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.68dec4ea.chunk.js.map